Yay! It's my birthday! Or it was my birthday a few weeks ago and you spoiled me with gifts.
So this is a special video. I want to thank every one of you for gifting me something
and I also want to show you some of the... whoops, where is it? Ah, is it here? I don't know.
I want to show you some of the things you gifted me. And I'm also still wearing my birthday crown
but we partied hard there was a bit of a loss anyway let's start so I turned 31
yes that's my age and I put a few things on my Amazon wish list of course mainly
fashion for example these two no handmade outfits one of them is a
catsuit really see-through mesh I'm going to make a jumpsuit up video with
this one but I think I'm going to change into this cute PVC dress now and then
I'm going to tell you about my birthday party. I'm already wearing the dress but
I want to add some shoes and I received a package from paradise with a super
cute birthday card. A paradise product I can't show you yet because not released
and also some shoes from my wish list. I think they fit the dress really good
because they're also PVC lookalike.
Okay, I like this combination a lot, the PVC dress from MyHandmade and these heels.
So finally some black shiny pointed basic heels.
And yeah, I celebrated kind of two days for my birthday.
So I had on Saturday and friends arrived Friday already.
We celebrated into my birthday.
We had a lot of fun.
And on Saturday we made a murder mystery dinner.
So we all dressed up.
And Fuxi was here for the weekend, Prüsi was here for the weekend and we had an awesome evening with the murder mystery dinner.
So yeah, I love that all of them showed up but also I love that you sent me so much stuff and that I can do this video now.
So thanks again.
when I'm talking about murder mystery and stuff. I also received this game from
one of my patrons. It's a card game based in the Cthulhu HP Lovecraft universe and
I think I'm going to play tonight. Now the dress is really short you may see
that I am covered in bruises. That is because I'm doing pole dancing at the
moment or I just started a few months ago and I also received some grip fluid
for pole so thanks for that I can really use that so I'm not gliding down the pole so much anymore
and also my daily go-to perfume which is already empty so not only fashion but also some practical
personal items thanks a lot and I think I'm going to combine something different
I destroyed my trusty Woolworth tights so thanks whoever sent me the new ones
and I also received this bodysuit and I think I'm going to pair them now
it's not a complete outfit of course but I just love these tights and for all of
you who are asking these are the Walford Neon 40 and they're super shiny. I paired
them with the bodysuit which is from Dominique and a lot of mesh is going on here.
So I think this is going to be a cool party outfit basic or cool basic in
general. I can also open it. So yeah I love both of them and when I'm talking about
the tights. I also got some stockings but I'm not trying them on yet so thanks a lot.
Yeah really excited because I didn't think that I would receive so many gifts to be honest
but I'm happy about all of them and from some I know what they gifted but from most of the stuff
I don't know who sent it so if you like to just let me know and tell me if you gifted me something and what it was.
Now it's all about the top because these are my leggings and my normal bra but it's a great way to show off your bra.
But yeah it's a basic fluffy see-through top from Aksami and I had this on my wishlist for a long time
because I thought this is a great basic piece and I still think I'm right.
I dig this look and I got some really cool accessories I want to pair with this look.
For one, when I've been to Malta I went into the guest store and saw a bag there but it was pink.
I was like this bag and black would be so great. So I put it on my wish list.
And here it is! Oh, I'm so happy! I love this bag so much!
It's black and gold and a real cool statement piece with the chunky chain here.
I want to look in the mirror myself.
Yeah, this is cool. Really, really glad someone of you gifted me this handbag.
still don't know who it was please let me know because ah this was so cool when
I unpacked it I unpacked everything on my birthday with the help of a foxy and
plushie yeah it was really fun also this week there came a package of sunglasses
also from Grasse so same brand than the bag this is going to look funny
Yes.
Oops.
Oh, and also, I received these gloves and I think they will match with the outfit because
of the leggings, but not with the bag because they're silver.
I managed to put them on.
It's a leather look, fingerless gloves
with built-in bracelets, so to say.
I think they're going to be a really, really cool accessory
I can use for a lot of looks.
So that's something I'm really looking forward to use too.
I'm really looking forward to use too
in other videos and for different stylies,
also for parties.
And let me check.
Yeah, I think I'm going to change into a catsuit now.
I received three catsuits.
Two of them are basically the same catsuit from Patrice Caranzalo.
One in PVC and one wet look.
And I also received this jumpsuit with spaghetti straps.
I think I'll show this one and jumpsuit up as well.
But I'm going to change into the wet look one.
Before I'm going to put on shoes,
I wanna point out how long this catsuit is,
like really long.
100 points.
And I received some New Demonia boots.
I've been looking for black shiny,
like high heeled boots for ages,
with which I can go partying.
Some that do not have any golden or silver accessories.
And these are the ones.
And the inside is red. I mean, how cool is that?
So I'm going to pair them really quick with this catsuit. Although, I would
probably not pair PVC and wet look in real life.
But yeah. I love these shoes! They have
little coffins on their buckles and
They have chains and they're so comfortable.
Like, the Monia shoes are the most comfortable shoes for going out and partying all night.
They did it again. Super comfy.
And as I said, the shoes are not going to match the catsuit.
But the catsuit I want to show to you.
It's a kind of a wet look fabric.
And as I already said, it fits really good.
also with really long arms and legs so yeah I can't wait to try the PVC one on
so I'm going to film the jumpsuit up soon I guess I think I've one outfit
left to show you I'm going to switch into that and then I'm going to tell you
goodbye and I'm not going to say which one it's going to be a fun surprise
aren't these pants fun? I don't know maybe I'll use them for pole dancing for
example or just to be blue and purple shiny. I don't know. They're fun. And I also put this t-shirt on my wish list
because I went to a Sisters of Mercy concert recently and they had only two
shirts in weird colors like neon orange and green and I was like meh. So I wanted
have a basic sisters of mercy shirt and yeah this was i think it was everything i showed you yeah
so thanks again to all of you i had a really fun time doing this video i had a really fun time
unpacking all these things and i will continue to enjoy them and you'll see most of them probably in
other videos so yeah thanks again and have a nice week see you in the next
video bye oh and by the way before I'm ending this video I think one or two
things are still in transit and still I don't know somewhere waiting to be
delivered to me so if I did not show something maybe it'll arrive just drop
me a message and tell me.